

Agena Gertrude Kristine

Freelance Graphic Designer

My Contact

agena.gertrude@gmail.com

09163326182

San Pascual, Batangas

(f) Gertrude Kristine Agena

Hard Skill

- Computer Literate
- Graphic Design
- Branding
- Social Media Marketing

Soft Skill

- Observation
- Decision making
- Communication
- Multi-tasking

Education Background

- Batangas State University NEU
 BS Information Technology
 Present
- Alangilan Senior High School (ASHS)
 Senior High School Science,
 Technology, Engineering, Mathematics (STEM) Strand
 Completed in 2023
- Batangas State University NEU
 Junior High School
 Completed in 2021

About Me

Gertrude Kristine Agena, an accomplished graphic designer with 3 years experience, is currently pursuing a BSIT degree. Her striking portfolio showcases expertise in graphic designing showing a strong mastery of Adobe Photoshop and other editing software. Eager to contribute to your company's visual identity and communication strategies, they are driven by professional growth and committed to making a significant impact.

Work Experience

Freelance Graphic Designer 2020 – Present

Key responsibilities:

- Creating Visual Design
- Understanding Client Requirements
- Meeting Deadlines
- Staying Updated on Design Trends and Software
- Managing Client Relationships and Business Operations

Supreme Student Government, Creative Member (ASHS) 2022 - February 2023

Integrated School Student Council - Board for Media Spectaculum Member (BatSU - NEU) 2019 - 2021

Key responsibilities:

- Content Supervision
- Editing and Proofreading
- Layout and Design
- · Meeting Deadlines
- Team Management and Leadership

Achievements

2021 - 2023	Graduated with Honor Junior High School & Senior High School
March 26, 2023	Civil Service Eligibility Professional Level Passer
2021 - 2022	Alangilan Senior High School Grade 11 - With High Honor
2021 - 2023	Alangilan Senior High School

Class President